Allen Jay Mortensen

1226 West Pitchfork Rd, Murray, UT 84123 yetti95@gmail.com Ph: 801-518-2480

Professional Summary

Quick to learn with 7 years' experience with running and managing a small Business and three employees. Recently switched from a bachelors in Aviation Management to a Bachelors of Computer Sciences and a Minor in Aviation Operations.

Skills

Computers and Electronics Service Orientation Administration and Management Judgment and Decision Making

Mathematics Active Learning Private Pilot **Instrument Rating**

Experience

Lawn Care Services AJ's Lawn Care

May 2010—Present Murray, UT

Owner and Manager of lawn care services of six lawns. Cut, trim and dispose of all trimmings. Any other yard work as needed. Maintain and repair all equipment. Have managed two other employees from time to time.

Warehouse and Delivery *Uintah Fasteners and Supply* *Apr 2011—Aug 2015* Salt Lake City, UT

Stock and organize all inventory. Pull and package fasteners for customer orders. Assist customers at Will Call counter. Delivery Truck driver.

Math Tutor AJ"s Tutoring Aug 2012 – Jun 2013

Murray, UT

Offered math tutoring in General Math, Pre-Algebra, and Algebra.

Drone Pilot/GIS Salt Lake County Surveyor's Office Sept 2017 - current Salt Lake City, UT

Map and script making for the Salt Lake Country Surveyor's Office. Flying drones, making 3d models, python scripts, and maps with the surveyor's office.

Owner/Drone Pilot

Sept 2017-Current

Alpha Drone Services

Salt Lake City, Ut

Owner and sole employee of alpha drone services. Flying drones, making 3d models, rectifying models to surveys and running the business in general.

Education

 $Leading\ Edge\ Aviation, Inc.$

Private Pilot License

High School Diploma

Murray High School

Aviation and Computer Science

Westminster College

Minor, Flight Operations

Currently working on a Major in Computer Science

Graduate date: May 12, 2018

Affiliations

Student Ambassador, People to People 2009-2010 Member, People to People 2009 - present

Salt Lake City, UT Aug 2013 Jun 2013 Murray, UT